Thank you for watching!
Here we go!
It's Musical Express Muscible!
Thank you very much.
Oh, yes, yes!
It's the end of the year already!
Terumi's arms are crossed.
Awww!
You don't talk this much with Omoto-san, do you?
Well, it's the end of the year.
I'd like to look back on the past year.
Oh, that's good.
I'm going to have some memories like this.
Oh, you're going to look back already?
Have you already?
No, it's just a little...
You're already looking back?
At the beginning of the year, we're all going abroad.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Masahiro was the most excited and scared.
Oh, that's right.
Then at the airport, Ryo-kun.
I remembered that I'm having fun.
If I told you at work there...
Oh, if I had said that...
Was it your first time abroad?
Second time abroad, I guess.
Why the recent photos?
What?
I was in the front seat on the plane.
Awww.
Just a quick picture of my face.
You look so cute out there.
Aww.
No, the view outside when we arrived is so beautiful.
I'm already doing lights and stuff, so I'm a person.
Well, it's like this.
It's a project to look back on this year. It's a project to look back on this year.
Oh, that's nice.
Yes, it's simple and good.
Yes, it is.
That's... I don't know, it's just a little bit too much to talk about in general.
What?
Let's pretend to be something else and look back on the year.
Oh!
I'm just going to be something...
Oh, thank God!
What the hell?
I can't wait to get some answers.
Yes, sir.
Maybe some aloha will come in.
Oh, I see.
One important thing.
Never laugh.
Oh, I can't.
Never.
Just looking back on the year, you shouldn't laugh.
Yes.
I'll even imitate this guy.
Ah.
But you should never laugh
Great. We shouldn't laugh at the end of the year.
Yes.
It's a lot.
It's a lot, that's for sure.
I love the feeling of holding back.
I love the feeling of being patient.
I can't lose with high blood pressure.
I'm scared
Don't laugh anymore, there's an offer on the table
I wonder when.
Um, everyone.
Seriously, please don't laugh. From here on out.
And those of you watching.
And those of you who get to see it. And those who could see it.
You should do it, even if you saw it.
All right.
Let's start from the tail moment.
Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
Oh, isn't it going pretty well?
You know, you say you can't stop laughing.
Oh, you're not supposed to eat.
Yes, sir.
Oh...
That kind of thing.
No such thing, right?
No such thing
Oh!
Okay, let's talk about...
Let's continue with the Thailand story.
Let's start.
It was my first time, too.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
It was great, wasn't it, Thailand?
Welcome.
We're here at the transsexual store.
It's a lot of fun.
First time.
Transsexual.
Time?
What's a transexual time show?
What? What?
A time show?
A transexual show?
What's time?
What's a time show?
A time show.
Transsexual show.
New New.
What was your favorite meal? What was the good meal?
Where was the food?
Thinhalf?
Thinhalf.
Beer?
Bee.
80 seconds!
Oh, man.
I don't want anyone to read my name.
And I really don't want to hear you say anything.
To the idiots.
Stupidly, everyone.
Don't laugh.
If you go to a transsexual show...
You don't get many chances to see that kind of thing when you're a spectator.
Oh, no?
No.
And the video...
It was really entertaining.
I'm going to dress you in something nice.
And the costumes.
Is this your first time today? I've never seen anything like that.
That's right.
She's probably a transsexual to begin with.
In the flesh.
It's not good to see them live.
But you know what?
I get it.
In Thailand, you went to Azorro, right?
Azorro. Where? Where?
Beach. Beach. Beach.
Phuket.
Come on. It looks good.
Looks good.
I thought you were going to try the food.
It looked delicious.
What's delicious?What's so good about it?
No, I don't know much about it.
Canned goods
Ochre.
Hmm?
Oh, me?
You've seen Camperture? Camperture?
Oh, man, I didn't even look at it.
Oh, you didn't dye it?
Too soon.
Not even close.
The show was fun to begin with.
It was the first three days.
The show was fun.
What was it like?
Like that one over there?
Kisses.
Announcements?
Wait a minute.
Yes!
Announcement?
You're smiling.
It's my favorite memory of the year.
I don't care if it's for work.
Or your personal life.
We all have our own memories.
Memories...
Hmm...
We had a field day, didn't we? Yes, we did.
Just the other day, yes
When I was a leader there
It was memorable.
I think it was good.
I was pretty cool.
I was on the blue team.
It was pretty scary.
I didn't say so. I didn't say so.
you know what?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Well, let's just call it a memory.
The best memory of the year.
We won, right?
Oh, yeah, we were a team.
We won the relay, too.
We were on the red team.
Red team, right.
How was it, Fujiko?
What? What?
What would you have done if you had a field day?
Field day
Item
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Are you scared?
In private
Oh, change and growth in my private life
Aren't you being too detailed?
Tell me a little bit.
I'd like to hear about it. I'm sure this is what it looks like.
Kosugi Dai, let's keep it like this.
No way! That's not right!
Dai Kosugi...
Dai Kosugi used to do it.
Kosugi used to do it all the time!
What did you do? Kosugi Dai.
Well, for example, something...
And fish!
Oh, you were a fish guy?
What does it matter if it's a nice fish?
Oh, it wasn't really.
I'll try that.
~~
Ah! Ahh.
Well, the three of you in particular, you've changed quite a bit.
Yeah, yeah.
You started living on your own.
I moved to Tokyo.
That was the biggest one.
How old are you now?
I'm 18.
Eighteen?
Living alone?
Seriously, so do Watanabe and the others.
It's amazing.
Two people living together?
Sign up!
Come on, let's go! Feeling!
Dark strapping!
Isn't that great!
Yeah, it's awesome!
Once?
Yeah, once.
Is this what he looks like?
I think I'm there.
It's perfect.
It's the same subject.
So many subjects.
A lot of the same themes.
Give everyone the same theme
Unique theme to talk about
Unique theme
The best thing you bought this year
Everyone's definitely bought something this year.
Definitely.
There's always something.
Like detergent.
Get some detergent.
Hello.
What?
What? What?
what?
Ha-ha.
It's 4 o'clock.
Four o'clock.
That's a four o'clock sound.
Parker-ing.
All right, all right, all right.
Oh, shit.
Just like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was a dollar off.
It was a dollar off.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you very much for watching.
Shoo!
Hashishu~~
Yiải
Yossi.
But you got me a Prestige too.
Wai-bu wai-bu.
Wai-bu?
Wai-bu.
Henseli.
Zelt.
Wow.
How many Playstations did you buy?
One PlayStation.
Heisei.
Oh, come on.
It's basically one.
What's this?
Two?
Prestige, volume 2.
Prestige, volume 2. Prestige Volume 2
Boo.
Ah Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2 Prestige Volume 2
Ding-dong.
Having fun?
Mika...
Mikaga
Squid Tangerine
What happened to me?
Oh, I was stretched a little.
What about you?
What happened to everyone?
Oh, Kuzuto-kun, you went away.
shall point
AEE, EEE, CREAM!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
What's next?
I want to work as a model.
Is that the boss?
You're not the president.
I've never seen a boss like that.
Hmm?
I have.
Yes, I am. In 2020.
Three years ago.
2024, right?
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I'm sure he laughed the most.
I've asked him to decide.
I'll have them announce it now.
That person...
I'd like you to draw one of these.
The last one of the year.
Closing Closing
This is the last of the YouTube
Here it is.
I don't care if you close it.
I'm going to lead it into 2014.
I see.
I'll let you say it.
Okay, everyone.
Are you ready?
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, then.
Let's see what you've got.
Let's go in.
We did it!
That's nice.
Still...
You're the one who's looking back and smiling.
What do you think about that?
I don't know.
Can I try to explain myself?
Oh, no!
Sure.
I'll go then.
Okay.
Are you sure you want to go there?
Mr. UNESCO.
Yes, well, let's see...
Yes, yes, yes, 2023.
Yes, it was fun. Yes.
It's been a really fun year.
It was a really fun year, yes.
2024, also a lot of
Strawberries, yes, strawberries
Hachigo, Hachigo
Hachigo, yes, Hachigo
I hope to see many more
We'll do our best, too We'll do our best.
Just tell me you're running an errand.
See you next year
Happy and smiling, yes!
Thank you very much.
I have to go to the Eiffel Tower.